[ thunder rumbling ]
[ thunder continues  rumbling ]
[ switches click ]
[ static, garbled voices ]
[ man, muffled ]  one, two, three, four, five.  Solid.
[ clears throat ]  one, two, three, four, five.
[ static,  garbled voices continue ]
[ man #1 ]  just stay out of trouble.
[ man #2 ]  that's easy for you to say.
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ lighter clicks ]
[ gasps ]
[ kisses ]
Hurry up.
[ footsteps departing ]
[ door opens, closes ]
[ footsteps ]
♪ [ pop ballad ]
[ woman ]  ♪ diamonds are forever
♪ they are all I need  to please me ♪
♪ they can stimulate  and tease me ♪
♪ they won't leave  in the night ♪
♪ I've no fear  that they might ♪
♪ desert me
♪ diamonds are forever
♪ hold one up  and then caress it ♪
♪ touch it, stroke it
♪ and undress it
♪ I can see every part
♪ nothing hides  in the heart ♪
♪ to hurt me
♪ I don't need love
♪ for what good  will love do me? ♪
♪ diamonds never
♪ lie to me
♪ for when  love's gone ♪
♪ they'll luster on
♪ diamonds are forever
♪ sparkling round
♪ my little finger
♪ unlike men  the diamonds linger ♪
♪ men are  mere mortals who ♪
♪ are not worth  going to ♪
♪ your grave for
♪ I don't need love
♪ for what good  will love do me ♪
♪ diamonds never  lie to me ♪
♪ for when love's gone
♪ they luster on
Remember your training.
Don't speak.  Don't make eye contact.
Don't move a muscle,
No matter what you see...
Or hear.
♪ and ever
[ beeping ]
[ line ringing ]
[ click ]
[ child ]  hello?
Hey. It's your dad.
Who?
You know your father.
Um, he's at work  right now.
C-can you just, um,
Go get your mom?
Um, uh... Yeah.
Mom!
Hello?
Hey.
Who's this?
It's me. I just got out.
[ sighs ]
[ click ]
[ line beeping ]
Fuck.
[ door lock buzzer buzzes ]
[ engine idling ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ thunder continues rumbling ]
Look, I kept my mouth shut. What does he want from me?
I don't even know where they are.
Geez!
Ohh!
This is your idea of shelter?
It's got potential.
Please. It's a shit-hole.
[ chuckles ] nothing that can't be fixed.
Fixed?
It should be condemned. Really?
How's betty ford?
Still a raging cunt.
So how long before the orderlies realize that you're missing?
Eh, they're not paid enough to care.
So, what kind of racket are you pulling here?
What makes you think that there's a racket to be pulled?
For one, the kitchen is derelict.
And two, you didn't buy this place to sling hash.  I know you.
You know me? Mm-hmm.
Well, you know, keep your friends close.
You don't keep friends. What's that supposed to mean?
[ chuckles ]
Present company excluded, of course.
Of course.
I mean, it's been a while, but I still know when you're bluffing.
Really? What's my tell?
[ laughs ]
Well, you know, if, uh--
If I told you that, it'd be a lot less fun for me,
And that's just notthe way I ro--
[ laughing ] well!
This is unexpected.
How subtle.
I mean, the architecture is a little too ming dynasty, don't you think?
Not exactly japanese.
It's a work in progress.
And you have party favors.
Which one of your goons picked her out?
I did.  Mm-hmm.
And is she, uh, full service, as they say?
Maybe.
Maybe?
It depends.
Depends on what? Don't be so cute.
It depends on how the night goes.
Mmm. Ah.
Who are we waiting on?
You'll see.
Oh, you know I hate surprises.
What is she, a fucking vegetable?
She's supposed to be.
You need to think of her as, uh, an edible plate.
In that case, I'd like to skip dinner and go right to dessert.
Mm-mm-mmm.  Sushi's free. Girl's not.
Oh. Even for an old friend?
House rules.
Domestic or imported?
Everything is imported.
How come she isn't a soy nigger?
I'm sorry.
A soy what?
[ laughs ] I'm just sayin'.
I know you like the yellows.
I only like one shade of yellow.
But comfort women come in many colors.
Well, either way you put on a good show.
[ chuckles ] I do try, crow.
No, no, I-I mean it.
Place like this, could have been laundry or the shake.
Something classy.
[ laughs ] until I saw the inside.
Never would have pegged it for a--  [ man ] whorehouse?
- [ snaps fingers ]  - [ chuckling ]
Or a meat market.
Take your pick.
I'll take both.  [ laughs ]
Would it have killed you to knock?
What the fuck is he doing here?
Same thing you are.
Come on.
No, I don't drink. Bad for the job.
You're not on the job yet.
Well, to old times, I suppose?
Nice to see some things haven't changed.
- Eat my shit.  - Charming.
Children, play nice.
- I'm not working with this faggot again.  - Have another drink, max.
- Why is he here?  - We need him.
He'll just bitch out again. You know that.
Hello. I'm standing right here.
You're a fucking pussy.
Oh, are you still upset about the nose?
[ cup slams on bar ]
What the fuck is this?
What does it look like?
Looks like four-fifths of a reunion...
At a titty buffet...
In tiananmen square.
Well, hello back.
Glad to see we're all up to our usual tricks.
[ chuckles ]
Who's filling in for the jailbird?
Nobody.
Thought you said this was a five-man thing.  It is.
Jailbird flew the coop.
No!  It's the truth.
- It's only been six years.  - Good behavior.
That's total bullshit.
What'd you do?
Not as much as I thought I'd have to.
[ scoffs ]  man, you know I'm--
I know...
That you've been off the wagon for about what,
Five months?
Don't you insult me.
Besides, you do want to be here to celebrate...
Our little jailbird's return to freedom tonight, don't ya?
[ max ]  more.
You didn't say the magic word.
Fuck you. Fuck the magic word.
Where's the fifth wheel? I want to get paid.
Relax. You can give him a few more minutes.
He just got out. You know how that goes, don't you?
Well, his daddy did.  [ laughs ]
[ grunting ]
I warned you the last time.
[ shouts ] max!
Control yourself.
That's all you got, huh?
Uh, crow.
What?
Oh, christ. Where's the bathroom?
[ laughing ] right over there.
[ whimpers ]
Ain't no glory hole in there, if that's what you're looking for,
You fuckin' puss.
So... It's gonna be one of those nights.
You know, if we're gonna be opening up old wounds,
Don't you think we should have a little bit more privacy?
Yeah, well, we're not gonna talk about all this in front of her,
Are we?
You don't have to worry about her.
[ scoffs ] why?
Because you own her?
What's the matter? You don't trust my powers of persuasion?
[ inhaling deeply ]
Besides, we're just waiting for the party to get started.
Ain't that right, fish?
What is this?
What is it?  [ chuckling ]
Your welcome back party.
Surprised?
Couldn't you have gotten me some strippers or a hooker or something?
[ crow ] oh, I'm sure duke could arrange that...
After dinner.  [ chuckles ]
[ crunching ]
Welcome back, fish.
Have a drink with us.
Do I have a choice?
It's wicked good to see you.
I wish I could say the same.
Oh, come on.
Let's not get off on the wrong foot, shall we?
Let's have a proper toast.
To old friends...
[ clink ] and fallen comrades.
Mmm.
Who's hungry?
Yeah. Wouldn't want it to get cold.
Nah, the fancy plate will keep it warm.
It's sushi, genius. It's served cold.
I know.
Crow.
How quaint.
Really?
Ah-ah-ah. Ow! What the fuck?
This is a special occasion.
Let's be civilized.
You want to say grace first?
[ sighs ]
Tonight is the first night in six years...
That our boy fish has breathed free air.
I thought we might do something unique.
Six years, five months and 17 days,
If you count from the time of the arrest.
Ah.
Well, this lovely array of sushi isn't just a pretty platter.
No, it's dessert too. [ chuckles ]
Tonight we dine yakuza style.
The outermost portions contain your standard "plain jane" sashimi.
But as we move inward toward the erogenous zones,
The meal becomes more... Adventurous.
The innermost portion contains the pot of gold.
Fugu, as they call it, is a yakuza delicacy.
Fubu.
Fu...
Gu.
Poisonous blowfish.
At its best, it numbs your lips,
Gives you heart palpitations,
Makes you feel like you've touched death and lived to talk about it.
At its worst, well--
Hundreds die in japan every year from eating it.
It's a test of mettle in their culture.
We start on the outside and work our way in.
The closer we get to the fugu,
The more exotic the flavor...
And the more of a man you are.
[ chuckles ]  I'm pissin' my pants.
Yeah. Laying it on a little thick there, duke.
All of this is for me?
You know, maybe I should have mentioned this before, but, um...
I fucking hate sushi.
[ francis exhales ] too bad. More for the rest of us.
I can't wait to eat shredded blowfish off a warm cooter.
Ooh, I'd buy that for a dollar.
[ exhales ]
[ chopsticks clattering ]
Aw, what the f-- fuckin' jap bullshit.
Where are the goddamn forks?
[ crow ]  so let me get this straight.
You can kill a man with your bare hands,  but you don't know how to use chopsticks.
Fuck with me again.
Gentlemen, yakuza don't bicker like this.
Aw, fuck the yakuza! Where's my money?
Max, sit.
Sit!
[ grumbles ]
[ duke ] let's not play the blame game tonight, okay?
Not before this wonderful meal that we're about to receive.
Everything will be evident in time.
I don't have 'em.
Eat.
Huh?
We got all night to talk about everything that happened...
Six years,
Five months  and 17 days ago.
I don't have them.
Look, I kept my mouth shut.
I did my time.
I just want to go home.
I said I'd like to enjoy this meal.
If this is supposed to be my last supper,  let's just cut to the fucking chase.
All right, fish.
If you insist.
What do you want from me?
There's a few loose ends that we need to tie up.
Loose ends?  [ crow ] yeah, you know.
Those little sparkly loose ends in that bag.
The cops took 'em.  They're the only loose ends.
[ max snickers ]
Them ends ain't loose no more.
And they didn't know shit.
Where's my money?
Do you really think I would try to rip you all off?
I just wasted the last six years of my life protecting all of you.
That's no absolution. We want what's owed us.
And I want my six years back, but I ain't gonna get 'em.
Just like you're not gonna get your fuckin' diamonds.
Spare us the sob story and tell us the truth.
What do you think the truth is?
You think I magically stashed the diamonds a block away from where the cops got me?
What am I, fucking harry houdini?
Papers say all you had was an empty bag.
Man, fuck the papers.
Papers say those cops were innocent.
How about it, max?
Were they really innocent?
Did you even let them talk before you mangled them?
[ chuckles ]
Man, I saved all you motherfuckers from prison.
We appreciate that, fish.
We really do.
But we want our cut.
Yes. Our cut.
How do you know max didn't kill the cops and take the money for himself, huh?
What? Fucking cocksuc--
Max!  Stop! Please!
Or maybe crow. Maybe he paid 'em off.
And maybe francis snorted it all away.
Oh, fuck you.  [ fish ] yeah! Maybe!
Or-- or maybe you--  maybe you--
Enough!
I'm gonna ask you nicely one more time.
Tell us where the diamonds are.
Keep yourself in one piece.
We'll even let you keep your share.
I can't.
[ metal clinks ]
I think you can.
How many of those are you planning on actually using?
All of 'em.
Fuck.
Hey, you goddamn cokehead, I gotta take a shit!
- He's been in there 20 fucking minutes already.  - Chill.
[ knocking ]
Hey, scarface, are you done in there or what?
You've made it this long. What's a few more minutes?
I downed half a bottle of laxatives this morning, asshole. What do you think?
[ laughing ] what the hell'd you do that for?
You always clear your shitter before a job.  [ stomach gurgles ]
- What?  - Just--
Goddamn, you are fucking green, aren't you?
- Ever hear of vinnie parker?  - No. Who the fuck is vinnie parker?
Aw, fuckin' shit. Not this again.
Jesus, if I had a dollar for every time I've heard this story--
I have it memorized.
Okay--
Once upon a time,
There's this cat-- vinnie fucking parker, right?
This guy is the best driver in town.
He's like a--  a born motorhead, right?
I mean, crazy about this shit.
Woulda barebacked mario andretti if he got the chance.
[ stomach gurgles ]  so...
[ exhales ] he goes out...
With the munsey twins, couple of retards,
On this big brinks gig couple years back.
Heist goes bad.
Couple of chicks get shot or something, I don't know.
But thanks to vinnie parker, they get away with almost two million cash.
Yeah.
Not even 10 minutes into their fuckin' freedom,
Goddamn donald munsey, like the fuckin' idiot retard that he is,
H-h-he looks out the window and makes eye contact...
With this beat cop on the sidewalk, right?
Cop recognizes him, calls it in and the next thing you know,
They've got the entire fucking force up their ass.
[ stomach gurgles ] [ groans ]
Oh, fuck. You gotta be kidding me.
So anyway, vinnie fucking parker leads them on this amazing five-hour chase,
Only to run out of gas in the middle of the san fernando fucking freeway.
Okay? He jumps out of the car, guns are blazin'.
None of these guys want to go back to the joint, of course.
Sure enough, vinnie parker ends up with two bullets in his face...
And his bowels release all over the goddamn scene.
Oh, you think that's funny, cupcake?  [ muffled laughter ]
Listen to me. He held that shit all day!
He thought he was gonna get to go after the gig. But he was wrong, wasn't he?
Sure, and some fucking 'copter overhead catches it,
Airs it on the 6:00 fucking news.
Poor vinnie, laying there dead--
Blood oozin' out of one end,  piss and shit flowin' out of the other--
And it's all over the goddamn 6:00 news.
[ chuckling ]  I just--
You know, I wasn't expecting it to go in that direction.
His mama saw that shit.
Literally.
Look, I don't know about you assholes,
But if I get my ass shot off on a job,
I sure as shit want to go out with a little fucking dignity, okay?
Get the fuck outta the way, asshole!
[ door slams ] laxatives again?
Wow.
All right, gentlemen, come and get your masks.
What the fuck?
Hey, these are classic noh theater masks.
Yeah, "no" is right. I'm not wearing that faggot shit.
Can't we wear hockey masks or ski masks?
This is my job. It's my rules.
Shit, I'd wear panty hose on my face, man!
No one needs to hear what you do for fun on weekends, max.
Har-dee-fucking-har.
Here you go, max.
You get to wear the okame, because you're so chipper.
Fuck me.
[ sighs ]
Crow? Yes?
You get to wear the kitsune.
Why?
Because you're so sly.
Oh, I get it.
[ chuckling ] francis.
The tenis for you.
It should be self-explanatory.
[ chuckles ]
Asshole.
The    saru is for nelson.
Ah.
The    hannis for me.
And fish, the rookie, gets to wear the sambaso.
[ toilet flushes ]
Everything come out okay?
[ sarcastic chuckle ]  you got a little something on your nose, asshole.
Hey. Hey. Here.
Pull the van around front. All right?
[ claps twice ]
Let's roll.
Don't forget your mask.
[ clapping ] come on, fellas!
[ door opens ]
Give me your gun.
Why?  [ door closes ]
Just give me your gun.
Here.
What the fuck is this?
New guy always has a little gun.
Eh?
Plus, you're the bag man.
That means you might turn traitor on us.
Small gun, small bullets, no traitor.
Yeah, well, I don't want to be the bag man then.
- You ain't got a choice.  - Why not?
Because the new guy is the most expendable.
Let's go.  [ exhales ]
[ door opens ]  [ chuckles ]
Don't worry about it, new guy.  It's all part of the initiation.  [ door closes ]
Yeah, I got that.
It's just, when you mentioned we'd be wearing disguises,
This is not what I had in mind, you know?
Well, that's duke for ya.
Larger than life.
Come on. Time to get to work.
[ door opens ]
[ exhales ]
[ frequencies squawking ]
[ grunting ]
[ rustling ]
That's it.
Is the party over already?
I really wish it hadn't come to this.
But you don't leave us many options.
Man, I told you everything I know.
I got something I want to show you.
You know what this is?
What's that, a trick question?
Answers, not attitude,
Is the name of the game tonight...
- [ bell dings ]  - fish.
You have me tied to this chair.  I'm a little disadvantaged.
Funny you should say that.
[ coughing ]
You ever been to pittsburgh?
Never. Mmm.
Dirty town. Rotten to the core.
Rusted over, covered in soot.
My papa used to pour slag in a steel mill.
You ever seen the inside of a steel mill? Huh?
Well, I have.
The old man used to drag me down to work with him.
Hotter than hell.
[ sniffs ]
Smelled like fire and sweat.
People walking around with blackened faces, sad eyes.
What's this got to do with the timer?
I'm getting to that.
Stop wasting my time.
Be careful what you wish for.
Me and that clock have shared a lot of time together.
See, when all you do for a living is poke lava...
In a coal-powdered asshole in pennsylvania,
You develop some nasty habits.
I used to be deathly afraid of that timer...
Because whenever it went off, it meant my ass.
My daddy, he got it from a p.O.W. Camp outside of hiroshima.
He used to scare me to death with stories about the "savage yellow man"...
Relentlessly beatin' the shit out of him.
[ laughing ]
He should have been around when we dropped the bomb.
Whenever I complained, he said I had it easy.
I ain't had no gratitude 'cause I ain't seen no prison camp.
That's why he took me down to the mill--
Teach me some respect.
My father gave me three minutes on that timer to show some respect.
And if he didn't like...
What I had to tell him by the time he heard that... Ding--
[ sighs ]
I tried my best to cover the bruises.
Eventually, it didn't matter what I said or did.
He'd just set the timer back to three minutes.
Until one day, I set that timer.
He didn't lay a finger on me after that.
He didn't pour no slag no more either.
I stuck around long enough to watch his ashes mix with that black cloud...
Spewing from the belly of that steel mill.
And then I split.
[ inhales, exhales ]
I had to find out where this came from.
I had to discover the culture...
That had inspired so much hatred...
In my daddy.
I had to go back to ground zero.
And you know what I found out?
Hmm?
That I was just like them.
Perhaps this timer...
Is my very first trophy.
I'm gonna take one from you...
If you don't give up those diamonds.
[ winding ]
[ ticking ]
[ dings ]
You got three minutes.
[ ticking ]
Okay.
Who's first?
I'm going.
No.
I called it.
You called it?
[ snickers ]  fuck.
I'm not scared of you.
Not yet...
Douche.
You know, your tough guy act's a real charmer, max,
But it's not gonna get us our money back.
- Is this really necessary?  - Do you want your share or not?
Yeah, but come on, man.  He's one of us.
"one of us"?
You barely know the asshole!
What if he really doesn't know? Huh?
- What'd you say?  - [ scoffs ]
What if it was you?
[ laughs ] hey, if it was me, I wouldn't be here.
[ thump ]
Oh, fine. Fuck it. Whatever.
Take it away, big boy!
This isn't gonna get you your money.
No?
No.
[ laughs ]
Convince me.
No, no, no, no. Let's not be premature.
Give him his time.
Follow the rules.
You were the one that interrogated the cops.
What did they say?
Well, don't matter what they said.
Can't trust a dirty cop, now can ya?
[ laughs ]
Besides, if they had the stuff, oh, I woulda gotten it from 'em.
You can do whatever you want to me, max.  It ain't gonna get you paid.
[ sighs ] maybe not.
[ grunts ]
I'm gonna have me some fun anyway.  [ laughing ]
[ groans ]
[ dings ]
Goddamn it, that felt good.
[ snickers ]
[ groaning ]
[ screaming, sobbing ]
I'm gonna give you till the count of three.
[ gasping, groaning ]  one.
Two.
okay.
[ snap ]  [ screaming ]
Time!
[ grunting, panting ]
- [ screaming continues ]  - that's enough.
Jesus.
[ fish gasping, panting ]
[ winding ]
[ ticking ]
Bravo, slapsie maxie!  Well done!
You really pulled it out of him there, huh?  [ cackling ]
- Like you could do better.  - Oh!
Is that a challenge?
Damn right it is.
Well... You wanna put some money on it?
You're gonna bet on this?
It's torture.
Oh, no, it's not.
Not yet anyway.
You ain't getting soft on us, are you, francis?
[ scoffs ]
So how about it, big guy?  You want to wager which one of us cracks him first?
[ sniffs ]  how much?
A thousand?
[ blows raspberry ]  that's a fuckin' pussy bet.
All right, five.
Okay, faggot, you're on.
[ chuckles ]  oh, you are in deep doo-doo now, my friend.
Oh, duke.
Why didn't you tell me　you had...
All these fun playthings　here already?
[ chuckles ]
Oh!
You sentimental old slob.
You kept my old work shoes!
[ sighs ]  well...
This we'll have to save for later.
How about a little lesson in how to use chopsticks, max?
Motherfucker.
[ chuckles ]
So how about it, fishy boy?
Got anything to say?
Not to you.
That's too bad.
What the fuck are you gonna do with those, man?
Acupuncture.
How about it, fella?
Are you ready to stroll down memory lane?
[ spits ]
Fuck you.
Now, see, that is just a bad attitude.
[ timer dings ] [ screaming ]
[ screaming continues ]
Come on. Talk to me.
Anything coming to the surface in there?
[ whimpering, screaming ]
How about now?
[ whimpering ]
Nothin'?
Okay.
[ screaming ]
Now listen to me.
You start talking, the hammer goes away. All right?
Yeah.
Come on!
All right. Don't say I didn't warn you.
Wait! Wait!  Wait. Wait. Wait.
I remember.
[ crow ]  yeah? Yeah?
Yeah? Yeah?
[ crow ] what do you remember?
I remember-- yeah?
[ laughing ]  I fucked your mother.
Fucked my mother?
Fucked my mother.
I'll show you "fucked my mother."
- [ duke ] time!  - [ max snickering ]
I said time!
Aww!  [ laughing ]
[ laughing ]
[ laughing ]  max is right.
Crow.
You are a fuckin' faggot.
[ duke ]  crow.
Crow!
[ grunts ]
[ vehicle door opens ]
[ ignition indicator chiming ]
We're on the move.
♪ [ stereo: Rock ]
Ah!
Ohhh.
Oh, juicy.
Juicy.
Look at me.  Look at me.
Juicy, juicy. Look at me.
♪ [ stereo: Rock ]
Morris.
Yeah, baby. Yeah, yeah. Look at you.
So juicy.
Morris.
- Morris.  - What?
We got visitors.
Well, what are you looking at me for?  Why don't you get rabbi rojo...
And go out there and tell 'em to fuck off!
[ sighs ]
Schlomo!
What?
Plumbers?
Who called the plumbers?
You didn't block up the toilet again, did ya?
That shit's not kosher.
Hey! You can't park here.
Hey, asshole!  You can't park here.
What the fuck?
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
Hands up! Hands up!
I said fuckin' hands up!
I already pressed the alarm!  Police are gonna be here any minute!
You guys better get the fuck outta here!
Yeah, right. Get down!
Get down!
Don't you fucking move!
Now, you plan on getting any more wise ideas?
You-- you can't have 'em.
I am not asking! I'm taking!
You don't know who you're stealing from!
Clearly we're stealing from you.
You see this?
It's a souvenir.
I take one of these from everybody I kill.
Do you want me to take one from you?
You don't know what they'll do to me!
I'd be more worried about what we'll do to you, man!
[ man ] jesus christ, morris!
Just give this cock-nosed point break motherfucking wannabe the bag!
[ grunts ]  shut the fuck up!
Yeah! Shut the fuck up!
[ laughs ]
I don't have the key.
[ sighs ]
That's okay.
I do.
No.
[ gasps ]
No!
[ screaming ]
Let me give you a hand.
Oh, holy fuck!
Aw, man up.
Oh, christ.  Oh, fuck.
Fish, come on! Fish!
- Fish.  - Fish, you piece of shit.
- Fish!  - Fish!
Goddamn it.
Wakey, fuckin' wakey, man.  Come on.
Come on.
Be a big boy. Wake up for me.  Come on.
[ groaning ]
All right.
And we're back.
Nice try.  You sure he needed mouth-to-mouth though?
ah, bite me.
[ winding ]
[ fish sighing ]
[ timer ticking ]
You're on deck.
Why don't you go next?
I'm eatin'.
Don't want to get your hands dirty?
Why are you here, francis?
I mean, if you don't want to contribute,
Maybe you don't want your share of the profits.
Are you in, or are you out?
oh, I'm in.
But I'm sitting this round out.
I'm eating.
What are you gonna do, stink him to death?  [ laughs ]
[ glass shatters ]
[ shards clinking ]
I'm done with this sissy shit.
[ grunting softly ]
Suck my dick.
[ timer bell dings ]
What was that?
I couldn't hear ya.
[ fish groans ]
[ groans ]
Well, speak up.
[ blows landing ]  [ groaning ]
Say something, boy!
[ groaning ]
[ sobbing ]
[ duke ] time!
Max! I said time!
Fuck!
I hate this game!
Oh, now your sock is all wet.
Bummer.
Well, don't have a hissy fit.
Jesus christ.
Sit on my fucking fist, you pansy.
Oh.  you wish.
[ breathing heavily ]
You know what?
I think...
It's about that time.
[ duke ]  uh-uh-uh, crow.
Remember what we said about patience?
The timer still needs to be reset.
Get ready to pay up, maxie.
[ sighs ]
Hi there.
My goodness.
He really did a number on you, all right. Ooh.
Well, I'm afraid...
We're gonna have to take a closer look.
What's the matter, francis?
You don't have the stomach for this anymore?
Did I ever?
You didn't seem to have a problem with wanton violence six years ago.
Things are different now, man.
I got a kid to support.
Now open up, say "ahhh!"
Oh, come on.
Hey.
I'll give you a lollipop when we're done, huh?
All right. Now look.
We can do this the easy way, or we can do it the hard way.
Why'd you make us come here tonight?
I didn't make you do anything.
Why?
All right.
[ screaming ]
I thought you might want your cut.
You especially have been bitching about needing money.
Since when do you ever pony up for charity?
This is hardly charity.
[ screaming ]
There we go.
Attaboy.
I know what you're doing.
Is that so?
Is that what you told your friends outside?
[ ticking continues ]
- [ sobbing ]  - now...
Speak now, or forever hold your peace.
What did you say?
You heard me.
- [ bell dings ]  - [ screaming ]
Yep.
Just as I feared.
Mr. Tooth decay is on the March.
We're gonna have to remove another.
Where the hell you goin'?
The fucking bathroom.
Kid's got no respect for good entertainment.
[ sniffs ]
[ spits ]
[ vial shatters ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Daddy's a fuckup.
[ sniffing ]
[ heartbeat thumping ]
[ screaming ]
Ooh!
You know, the lack of dental hygiene...
In state prisons is a real travesty.
I think I spied some more cavities in there.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
What was that?
I'll talk.
I'll talk.  You will, huh?
Now, we've played this little game before, fish.
You remember what happens when you lie?
So, talk.
You were--  you were right.
I was?
Oh, well! Fancy that.
What about?
Diamonds.
You don't say.
I was--  I was running from the cops.
[ rattling ]
Snake eyes.
They were--  they were closing in,
So--  come on!
So?
[ whimpering ]
I had... No choice.
Where are they now?
Where did you put 'em?
I had... No choice.
Fish, where are the fucking diamonds?
Max! What the hell do you think you're doing?
Tell us what you did with our shit!
Where's my money!
Where's our money?
Fish.
Come on, fish.
Yes. Come on. Say something.
Aw, jesus christ.
Hey, hey, hey.  No, no. D-d-don't move. Don't move.
I'm gonna get an ambulance.
No, no, no.
[ groaning ]
Nelson, you fucking asshole!
Where the hell are we?
Go get those masks.
[ crow ] what's going on?  [ groaning ]
Shit!
[ groaning ]  aw, man. I think it's broken!
- [ sirens wailing in distance ]  - shit. Where they coming from?
North.
We gotta get out of here.
Nelson.
[ grunts ]  nelson!
- [ sirens wailing ]  - oh, fuck.
- Come on. Let's move.  - We gotta get out of here.
Ah, suck it up!  [ screams ]
That's my bad arm, you fuckin' douche bag!
- Aw, fuck me, man.  They're getting closer.  - Move, move!
Hey, rookie!  Bring me that fuckin' bag!
Ah, man! Shit! Shit!
[ sirens wailing ]  [ francis ] split up! Split up!
He's fuckin' dead.
You fucked up, mongoloid! He's dead!
What?
- He's dead!  - Are you sure?
I'm not a fuckin' doctor, but yes, I'm pretty fucking sure!
We needed him alive, max!  Oh, I knew it! I fucking knew it!
You fucked this up just like you fucked up with the goddamn cops.
I didn't fuck nothin' up. Bullshit.
Bull-fucking-shit! You are a fucking failure, man.
Just like your fuckin' father.
- You fucking--  - oh, oh, oh. Come on.
Ooh-ooh! Give me an excuse.
Ah. You pussy.
Don't you fucking get it, ya moron?
That's it. No more information.
Game over!
Get your fucking gun off me.
We get nothing now because of you.
We were never gonna get anything.
What the fuck does that mean?
It means this whole night has been bullshit.
I'm not doing this, duke.
You ain't got no choice.
I'm leaving.
- It ain't over, francis.  - It will be soon enough.
Oh, whoa. You got me by the balls, huh?
You thought I'd just let you walk out of here?
What the fuck's going on?
Tell them why we're really here, duke.
They know.
Do they? Loose ends?
Motherfuckin' diamonds.
When the fuck are you gonna wake up?
The only loose ends here are us.
What are you sayin'? We've been set up?
He brought us here to get rid of fish...
And then the rest of us.
That's a hard pill to swallow.
[ francis ] is it?
You're smart, crow. Do the math.
He paid off those cops to retrieve the loot and pin it on fish.
Same cops max got rid of.
Six years later,  fish gets out of jail, and we all end up dead.
He walks with our money, no questions asked.
No loose ends.
Wraps up nice and pretty, doesn't it?
Hmm. I guess this is the point where the police storm the building, right?
What? More cops?
Sure are. As a matter of fact,
They're listening in on our conversation right now.
Well, where are they, francis?
You're wired?
[ francis scoffs ]
Yeah. Right.
I'm fuckin' wired.
Why don't you just go ahead and unbutton your shirt.
When are you gonna open your eyes, crow?  You're a puppet.
Open your shirt.
How long are you gonna let him pull the strings?
Francis, open your goddamn shirt!
Or what?
You gonna shoot me?
If you're gonna shoot me, then shoot me!
[ max ] prove there ain't no wire, boy.
Maybe then we'll believe your bullshit.
Yeah, how about it, francis?
[ scoffs ] prove it to you?
What's the point, max?
You're even worse than crow.
At least duke talks to him like he's a real person.
I wouldn't go there if I were you.
You?
You're nothing but a dog.
Duke just snaps his fingers, and you run to do his bidding.
You're his fucking bitch.
How's that collar feel?
[ gunshots ]
[ groans ]
We were his bargaining chips.
More crooked cops waiting to take our cash.
Max, what the fuck are you doin'?
I'm tired of this cat and mouse shit.
I want my cut.
You don't want to do this.
I ain't your fuckin' dog.
Put the gun down.
This motherfucker has been holding out on us for six years.
[ laughs ] you actually believe that coked-up, lying piece of shit?
I don't believe any of you assholes.
Max,
If I wanted to kill you,
You'd be dead already.
[ max ] maybe.
Maybe not.
Max, put down the fuckin' gun.
Not till I get paid.
Listen, you stupid fuck. Francis was full of shit.
He's always been full of shit!
If he's so full of shit, where's his wire?
In the fucking bathroom, you neolithic 'tard.  He went to the bathroom!
- You're so fucking sure, ain't ya?  - Yeah.
Hey. When has duke ever steered us wrong, huh?
Don't matter. We ain't no three amigos here.
"all for one and one for all," my ass.
That's the three musketeers, you illiterate dunce.
You think you're so smart.
Think you're smart enough to dodge a bullet?
[ duke ] now, boys,
Let's not get out of hand.
Huh? How about that, faggot?
How smart are you?
Oh, I'm the faggot, am I?  Let me tell you how smart I am.
Smart enough to know what your daddy did behind closed doors.
Fuck you.
No. Fuck your daddy.
Just like he fucked you.
[ shouts ]
Fuck.
- [ groans ]  - [ clicking ]
[ groaning ]
Still standing.
Pussy.
[ wheezing laugh ]
Hey.
[ groaning ]
[ groaning continues ]
Oh, fuck.
I-I need a hospital.
Duke.  [ coughing ]
What are you doin'?
I need a hospital.
[ sobbing ]
Oh, come on, duke.
After all we've been through?
From the killing fields...
To the kill.
I stood up for you, asshole.
I loved ya, ya fucking son of a b--
[ thuds ]
Abayo.
[ whimpering softly ]
Hmm.
[ grunts ]
Well,
That went well.
It's just you and me now, kid.
[ cuff link clatters ]
It's unfortunate I didn't find out where my diamonds are.
So you'll have to be my consolation prize.
But let's not get ahead of ourselves.
A wise man once wrote,
"I cannot see her tonight.
I must give her up.
So I will eat...
Fugu."
[ snaps fingers ]  oh!
Simple pleasures.
Ooh.
That's more like it.
[ thuds ]
[ breathing erratically ]
Fugu can be quite satisfying.
But I didn't think...
That the toxin would get the better of you so fast.
- [ breathing erratically ]  - so,
We're gonna have to make this quick.
Oh.
Well, I bet...
If you could talk right now,
You'd be asking,
"why?"
Well,
Long story short, you took something...
That belongs to me.
[ whispers ] and I want it back.
[ cigar cutter clicks ]
So maybe this will jog your memory.
[ man breathing heavily ]  [ woman whimpering ]
Okay.
[ groans ]
Okay.  Hey, are you okay?
Are you all right? Yeah. Are you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
All right. We made it.
All right.  Now I'm gonna go check on them.
-Okay.  -Okay?
You're okay.
Just wait right here. I'll be right back.
[ gasps ]
[ sobs ]
[ sobbing ]
[ inhales, exhales deeply ]
[ crow screams ]  nelson, you fucking asshole!
[ francis ]  where the hell are we?  [ shouting ]
Hey, rookie!  Bring me that fuckin' bag!
[ francis ] shit! Shit!  [ sirens wailing ]
[ sirens continue ]  [ francis ] shit!
Split up!
You know,
I've never been much of a gambler,
But you--
You seem to be the type that likes to bluff.
Maybe you need a new game.
Chance--
[ bullet clatters ]is a real bitch.
One little thing can come along...
And ruin everything.
[ gun cocks ]
Six years ago,
I never imagined I'd be here.
I was so happy until you crashed into my life.
[ clicks ]
At first I thought,
Well, maybe...
I could buy happiness.
But some things just can't be bought.
[ gun clicks ]
Money can't buy my life back.
[ clicks ]
And money--
Money won't bring my love back.
[ clicks ]
But this--
This feels...
So good.
Please.
♪ [ blues ]
[ car engine starts ]
Where to now?
I just want to go home.
♪ [ continues ]
♪ [ man humming ]
♪ I just can't get over  losing you ♪
♪ so if I seem
♪ broken in two
♪ walk on by
♪ foolish pride
♪ is all that I have left
[ female backup singers ]  ♪ let me hide  ♪ so let me hide
♪ the tears  and the sadness ♪  ♪ the tears and the sadness
♪ you gave me  ♪ you gave me
♪ you put the hurt on me  you socked it to me, mama ♪
♪ when you said good-bye
♪ so, please, walk on by
♪ oh, mama
♪ make believe you never  see the tears I cry ♪  ♪ walk on by
♪ so I'm begging you to
♪ walk on by  ♪ walk on by
♪ oh, yeah
♪ and make believe  you never see  the tears I cry ♪
♪ walk on by
♪ so I'm begging you  I'm begging you ♪
♪ to walk on by  ♪ walk on by
♪ walk  ♪ make believe you never  see the tears I cry ♪
♪ walk on by
♪ oh
♪ there's no dust in my eye  ♪ walk on by
♪ oh, no
♪ the smoke  ain't makin' me cry  no, no, no ♪
♪ it's the hurt  you put on me ♪  ♪ walk on by
♪ I don't want you to see  this man cry ♪
♪ so, please
♪ walk on by  ♪ walk on by
♪ oh, honey, no
♪ walk on by
[ 雷声隆隆 ]
[ 雷声继续 ]
[ 开关声 ]
[ 电台调频的声音 ]
[ 男声，低沉的 ]  [ 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 连续 ]
[ 清一下喉 ]
[ 电台调频的声音继续 ]
[ 男声 #1 ]  快点排除问题!
[ 男声 #2 ]  你说得倒是轻松!
[ 雷声隆隆 ]
[ 打火机声 ]
[ 喘息声 ]
[ 亲吻声 ]
你要抓紧时间!
[ 脚步声远去 ]
[ 门打开，关闭声 ]
[ 脚步声 ]
寿司女孩 翻译: 玄子 校对: misssleep
♪ [ 流行民谣 ]
[ 女声 ]  ♪ 钻石恒久远
♪ 她是我所需  我所悦 ♪
♪ 她亦可鼓舞  戏谑我 ♪
♪ 她从未于夜晚离去
我也从未惶恐   也许有一天 ♪
♪ 她将弃我而去
♪ 钻石恒久远
♪ 轻举一枚  抓紧她 ♪
♪ 触摸她, 轻抚她
♪ 然后褪去她的外衣
♪ 在我面前一览无余
♪ 毫不保留
♪ 毫无心机。
♪ 我并不需要把我的爱
♪ 给予那些爱我的
♪ 钻石从未
♪ 对我说谎
♪ 说何时爱情远去
♪ 她会一直光彩照人
♪ 钻石恒久远
♪ 在我的指尖
♪ 闪闪发光
♪ 钻石源远流长
♪ 而芸芸众生
♪ 只不过尘归尘，
土归土
♪ 我并不需要把我的爱
♪ 给予那些爱我的
♪ 钻石从未对我说谎
♪ 说何时爱情远去
♪ 她会一直光彩照人
[厨师]: 别忘记你接受的培训
不能讲话，不能有任何眼神交流
不论你看见什么
或者听见什么
也要保持纹丝不动。
♪ 永远
[ 拨号声 ]
[ 电话响铃 ]
[ 接听 ]
[ 孩子 ]: 你好
嘿，是爸爸
谁?
你爸爸
哦，他现在在上班
那，那你能不能
让你妈听?
哦，好的
妈妈！
你好？
嘿
你是哪位?
是我，刚从牢里出来
[ 叹气 ]
[ 电话挂了 ]
[ 断线的声音 ]
干
[ 门开锁的声音 ]
[ 汽车引擎声 ]
[ 雷声 ]
[ 雷声继续 ]
看，我一直什么都没把他们抖出来。他们还想我怎么样?
我连他们在哪里都不知道
吉兹!
哦!
这里就是你找的好地方?
我会让它变好的
拜托，简直就是个大茅坑
[ 窃笑 ] 没什么东西是无法改变的
改变?
这应该快被拆掉了吧，不是吗？
贝蒂.福特怎么样了?
还是老样子吧.
你的那些人，需要多久才发现你不见了?
他们才拿那点钱，没空来理我
你打算怎么来好好利用这里呢？
你怎么知道呢？
第一点，那个厨房是空的
第二点，你不可能把这里买下来开个小饭馆吧，我太了解你了。
你懂我？哼哼.
好吧，你知道，你要多跟老朋友保持良好的关系
不珍惜友谊。那是什么意思？
[ 窃笑 ]
你不会去光顾礼品店，是吧
那倒是
我说，虽然有一阵没见了，但是我还是知道你在装神弄鬼
真的？我怎么了？
[ 笑 ]
好吧，你知道，如果-
如果我说出来了，那就没这么好玩了
而且那也不是我的风格--
[ 笑 ] 好吧!
这个 是怎么也没想到.
太精致了。
我的意思是，这装修也太中国(明朝)风了吧，你怎么看?
都不算是日式风格。
还没有完工。
你原来是要开派对阿！
哪阵风把她吹来的?
是我  哼哼
她提供全套服务吗？传说中的?
也许
也许?
看情况
看什么情况? 别这么搞笑了。
要看今晚怎么过的
恩。
我们还在等谁呢?
你马上就会知道。
哦，你知道我最讨厌惊喜了
她难道是个植物人吗?
这是她的工作。
你可以把她想像成，一道菜
如果那样，我非常乐意跳过我的主食，直接享用甜点
哼哼，寿司是免费的，美女可不是。
哦，即时是对一个老朋友也不免费吗？
这是规矩
这些东西是国产的还是进口的？
全部都算外国来的
那为啥她就不是一个亚洲人(黄豆比如黄色皮肤，nigger是对黑鬼的蔑称)
你说什么？
一个黄豆什么?
[ 笑 ] 我只是说
我知道你喜欢黄皮肤的.
我只是喜欢其中一个而已。
而且所有的肤种都会有好女人
好吧，不管怎么样，你策划得很完美
[ 笑 ] 我确实尽力了，克罗
不不，我意思是
像这样的地方，可能是洗衣房
或者是某种高级场所
[ 笑 ] 如果不是我亲眼所见
我可从来没想过这里能弄成一个--  [ 男声 ] “天上人间”
- [ 打响指 ]  - [ 笑声 ]
或者是一个“肉”市场
你自己做个选择
那我就两个都选  [ 笑声 ]
你敲个门会死吗？
你丫在这里干什么?
跟你一样
过来
我不喝酒，影响工作
你还没在工作中呢
好吧，我建议，为了美好的过去干杯?
很好，有些事情还是从来没变
你去吃屎吧  很好
兄弟们，客气点
我可不会再与这个“老玻璃”共事了  再来一杯，麦克斯
为啥让他也来这了  我们需要他的
他只会再添乱子，你知道的。
喂，我可正站在这里呢
你只是个傻X
哦，你还在为了那个鼻子的事情郁闷吗？
[ 杯子撞击吧台声 ]
搞毛子事情?
你觉得呢?
我觉得像在天安门广场
只有五分之四的
色情自助餐聚会
好吧，欢迎回来
很高兴又看到这些老花样
[ 笑声 ]
谁在填补那个牢里的家伙留下的空缺?
没人
- 我以为是五个人的聚会呢  - 没错
牢里的已经出来了
不  这是真的
- 这才六年而已  - 在监狱中表现良好
纯粹胡扯!
那你怎么办呢?
我也不会怎么样的
[ 一阵冷笑 ]  兄弟，你知道那个...
我知道...
你已经洗手不干了
都五个月了吧？
别不给我面子!
而且，你难道不想，今晚在这里..
为我们牢里兄弟重获自由，庆祝一下吗？
[ 麦克斯 ]  再来
你没说重点呢
该死的重点
那个小子在那呢，我要我的钱
放宽心，让我们再等他几分钟吧
他刚出来。你知道那回事的
好吧，他爸比他更清楚  [ 笑声 ]
[ 痛苦声 ]
我最后再警告你一次
[ 大声斥责 ] 麦克斯!
控制情绪！
你满意了吧？
哦，克洛
怎么了？
哦，天哪，洗手间在哪里呢？
[ 笑声 ] 那边
[ 啜泣声 ]
那边不就是你要的去DIY的地方
去你的
所以。。。今晚又是一个揭伤疤的时候
你知道，如果我们去揭开旧伤疤
你不觉得我们需要一点隐私吗？
是啊，我们不要在那个女人面前谈论一切
是吗？
你完全不必担心她
[ 冷笑 ] 为什么?
因为她是你的吗？
有什么关系?你不相信我的威慑力吗?
[ 深呼吸 ]
而且，派队马上就要开始
对吗，费什?
怎么回事?
这是什么?  [ 笑声 ]
你的出狱接风派对
惊喜吗？
你就不能直接送我个陪酒女郎或者舞女嘛？
[克洛] 哦，我确定杜克可能在晚餐后
已经安排了这些  [ 笑声 ]
[ 咬碎声 ]
欢迎回来，费什
跟我们喝一杯
我有的选嘛？
见到你太高兴了!
我也希望我能说一样的
哦，拜托阿
我们别搞砸气氛了
来一个正式一点的祝酒词
为了友谊
[ 碰酒杯声 ] 和一群堕落的兄弟们
恩
有人饿了吗？
是啊，再等的话，它们都凉了
不会，这个高级的盘子有神奇的保温功能
这可是寿司阿，本来不就应该是凉的
我知道
克洛
太怪了
不会吧?
阿欧，搞什么了?
在这么一个特殊的场合
文明一点
你要开了正式的开场白嘛?
[ 叹息声 ]
我想这是六年来第一次
我们的兄弟费什可以呼吸到自由的空气
我觉得我们可以做些特别的事情
六年，五个月，十七天
如果你从我们被捕那天开始算
啊。
好吧，排列有序的寿司可不仅仅是份漂亮的大餐
是啊，也是甜点 [ 笑声 ]
今晚我们用yakuza(日本黑帮)方式吃饭
最外围的部分是寻常的的生鱼片
但是，当我们慢慢移向"敏感地带"
美食就变得更加像...“探险”
最里面的部分就是所谓的“金矿”
他们称之为，Fugu(河豚肉)- yakuza的精髓所在
河部
河...
豚.
有毒的河豚
其中最好的一种河豚，它会麻痹你的嘴唇，
使你的心跳加速
让你如同触碰到死亡，又起死回生，来叙述感受
但是最坏的情形，也就是--
在日本，几百号人吃了它而丧生
在他们的文化中，这是一种属于勇者的游戏
我们从外围开始，然后慢慢往中间推进
越接近河豚
就越有异国情调
也越能证明你个真男人
[ 笑声 ]  我都要吓得尿裤子
是啊，你废话有点多了啊，杜克
这些都是给我准备的嘛?
你知道，我应该早点告诉你的..
我最讨厌的就是寿司
[ 弗朗西斯吹气 ] 太惨了，那我们得吃得更多了
我已经忍不住要吃那些里层的河豚肉了
哦，我也很愿意来一块
[ 喘气声 ]
[ 筷子掉下来的声音 ]
这是什么玩意
丫的就不能给我个叉子嘛？
[ 克洛 ]  那我恕我直说
你可以赤手空拳杀人，但是你不懂用筷子
你还想死一次嘛？
兄弟们，yakuza可不兴这一套
去你的yakuza，我的钱在哪里？
麦克斯，坐下!
坐下！
[ 嘟囔声 ]
[ 杜克 ] 我们今晚就不要再互相再互相抱怨了，可以吗？
起码不在这顿即将入口的美食之前
一切问题都会得会迎刃而接
我没有
吃饭.
什么？
我们有一整晚来讨论当年的事情...
六年
五个月十七天以前发生的
我确实没有
你看，我一直没把你们抖出来
我完成了我的使命
我现在只想回家
我说过我想好好吃这一顿
如果这算我最后的晚餐，那就直接点吧
好吧，费什
如果你坚持的话。
你到底想要什么？
我们的确有些未了结的事情
未了结?  [ 克洛 ] 是啊，你懂得
在那个包里闪闪发光的未了事
警察拿了，这是唯一的可能结局
[ 麦克斯窃笑声 ]
这是不可能的结局
他们不可能知道
我的钱在哪里?
你真的觉得我会背叛你们所有人吗？
我只不过浪费我生命中的六年时间来保护你们所有人
这个不是你能开脱的借口，我们要我们应得的。
我只想要回我的六年，虽然这是不可能的
就好像你们拿不回你们该死的钻石一样
省省你的血泪史，告诉我们真相吧
那你觉得什么是真相呢？
你觉得在警察抓住我的地方，我神奇地把钻石藏起来了?
我是魔术师胡迪尼吗？(harry houdini著名的马戏团魔术师)
报纸说你的包是空的
去他的报纸
报纸说那些警察是无辜的
你觉得呢，麦克斯？
他们真是无辜的嘛？
你在砍死他们之前跟他们聊过嘛？
[ 笑声 ]
我让你们所有人免受牢狱之灾
我们的确很感激，费什
真的
但是我们要我们那一份
是啊，我们那份
你怎么知道麦克斯没有杀掉警察把钱独吞了？
什么？欠揍嘛？
麦克斯！住手！
或者克洛。也许他用钱打点了警察。
也许弗朗西斯全部吸走了
哦，去你的  [ 费什 ] 是啊，也许！
或者是你--
够了！
我再最后很客气地问你一次
告诉我们钻石在哪里
如果你还想活着离开这里
我们还会考虑你的那一份的
我没有
[ 金属声 ]
我想你能做到
你打算用多少子弹
全部
嘿，在里面吸毒的家伙，我要用厕所
他已经呆在里面20分钟了  冷静
[ 敲门声 ]
嘿，你死在里面了嘛?
你都等了这么久了，再等几分又怎么样？
我早上喝了半瓶泻药，混球，你倒来试试看?
[  笑 ] 你有必要这样做呢？
我会在工作前把胃清空  [ 胃咕噜声 ]
- 什么意思?  - 就是--
晕倒，你是新来的吧？
- 你听过维尼.帕克嘛？  - 谁是维尼.帕克?
我倒，又要来这个了
我的天，如果每次听到这个故事我能赚一块钱就好了
我听了无数遍了
好吧--
很久以前
有个家伙叫维尼.帕克
他是城里最好的赛车手
他是天生的摩托党，懂吗？
我意思是，为了飙车而疯狂的家伙
如果他有机会，会成为不带头盔的马里奥·安德烈蒂（意大利著名车手）
[ 胃咕噜声 ] 所以
[ 呼气声 ] 好多年前，他和
一对叫蒙西的双胞胎，还有一些拖后腿的家伙，
开着他的Brinks的车，一起去打劫银行
但是抢劫进行得不太顺利
过程中几个劫匪还中枪了，具体细节我也不清楚
但是多亏有维尼.帕克，他们还是抢到了大约200万现金
是啊
还没逃掉10分钟，
多纳蒙西（双胞胎之一），跟白痴一样的人
他，他居然往窗外跟路边的警察
对视了一下
警察马上认出了他，然后后面你知道了
肯定是要倒大霉了，整个城的警察都在追他们
[ 肚子声，咕噜]
哦，开什么玩笑。
但是不论如何，维尼帕克带着他们经历了疯狂地五个小时的逃逸
直到在圣费尔南多的一个高速上，油已经耗尽了
他跳出车，跟警察开始交火了
当然，他们肯定不想被抓回去
总之到最后，维尼.帕克最后脸上中了两弹死了
他肠子里的东西被全被曝光在电视屏幕前
你觉得很好笑吗？小家伙？  [ 笑声 ]
你听我说，他可是憋了一整天的大便!
他以为搞定抢劫后就能拉了，但是他不是错了嘛？
居然还有直升飞机在拍摄当时的画面
6点的新闻播放出来了
可怜的维尼，躺在那死了--
血一滩，还屎尿一地
全部在6点的新闻里面
[ 笑声 ]  我只是--
我真没想到这个事情还会这样
但是他的老妈也看见了这一切
完完整整
我说，我不太知道你怎么想
但是如果我在工作中死了
我起码要讨回一点起码的尊严，好吗？
快点给我出来！
[ 门开了 ] 又吃了泻药?
瓦哦
好吧，兄弟们，过来拿你们的面具
什么东东?
嘿，这些可是经典“能剧”（日本歌剧）里的面具
是啊，就是“不”(不和能剧同音)  我才不戴这些同性恋面具
我们不能戴曲棍球或者滑雪面具嘛？
这是我的地盘，我定的规矩
我情愿头上套丝袜!
没人关心你周末的娱乐，麦克斯。
你敢再说一遍
你的，麦克斯
你戴“奥卡美”(来自日本神话)，因为你就是这么爽快的
我去!
[ 叹息 ]
克洛? 好吗？
你戴狐人面具
为什么?
因为你很狡猾
好，我懂了
[ 笑声 ] 弗朗西斯
面具“十”是你的
不需要多说明了吧
[ 笑声 ]
去你的
撒鲁是给尼尔森的
阿
“汉恩”是我的
费什，菜鸟， 戴“三番三”面具
[ 冲马桶声 ]
全都拉出来了嘛？
你鼻子上有东西
嘿，嘿，这儿
车子停在前面，好吗？
[ 拍手两次 ]
各就各位
别忘记你的面具
[ 拍手 ] 加油，伙计们!
[ 开门声 ]
[ 给我你的枪 ]
为什么?  [ 关门声 ]
赶快给我你的枪
这个
这是啥玩意?
新人配小枪
哦？
另外，你是背包男
因为你也可能背叛我们
小枪，小子弹，不准背叛。
好吧，我可不想做个背包。
- 你没有选择  - 为什么没有?
因为新人最不可靠
出发
[ 开门声 ]
别担心，新人一开始都这样  [ 关门声 ]
是啊，我懂了
只是你们说要乔装的时候
我可没想到是这样的面具
好吧，这可是杜克给你的
为了保住你的小命
赶快，工作时间到了
[ 开门声 ]
[ 喘气声 ]
[ 关门声 ][ door closes ]
[ 雷声 ][ thunder rumbling ]
[ 瑟瑟声 ][ rustling ]
[ 呼呼声 ]
[ 瑟瑟声 ]
搞定！
这个派对算结束了嘛?
我真的不希望落到这个地步
但是，是你没给我选择
老大，我已经坦白了一切
我有样东西给你看
你知道这个是什么嘛？
这是什么，恶作剧问题嘛？
回答我的问题，不是问你观点
今晚游戏的名字。。。
- [ 铃声 ]  - 费什
你把我绑在椅子上，我明显丧失了一点优势
这么说很有意思
[ 咳嗽声 ]
你去过匹兹堡嘛？
没去过
罪恶之城，堕落到极点
腐朽不堪
我爸爸曾经在里面炼钢厂里倒岩渣
你见过炼钢厂内部嘛？
好吧，我是见过的
我老爸居然把我抓进去跟他一起工作
那里比地狱还要热
[ 吸气 ]
整天都是弥漫着火的味道和汗水味
到处都是烧伤的脸和痛苦的眼神
你的故事跟这个计时器有什么联系?
我马上讲到那个了
不要浪费我的时间
珍惜你说话的机会
我和我的计时器可是很有故事的
当你在宾夕法尼亚州的一个煤渣洞里，为生存所做的一切，
就是捣岩浆
我养成了一些很不好的习惯
我曾经很害怕计时器
时间一到，意味着我的屁屁要倒霉了
我爸爸，他从广岛的一个战俘营里得到
他曾经用它编了一个“野蛮的黄种人”的故事来吓唬我
在监狱里，他们残酷地鞭打他
[ 笑声 ]
当美国向广岛扔原子弹的时候，我觉得他肯定就在附近
他总是让我不要抱怨太多，这些都是小菜一碟
我没有经历他那段监狱生活，我根本不懂
这就是为什么他把我带下这个地狱
教我学会尊重
我爸爸给我三分钟，定在这个钟上，显示了对我的尊重
但是如果
他不喜欢我在这个三分钟里面给的解释，那当这个“叮”响起的时候
[ 叹息声 ]
我已经尽力做到最好，免受皮肉之苦了
但是到了后面，不管我说什么，或者做什么
他只是重新设三分钟
直到有一天，轮到我来设三分钟
他之后再也没有动过我
他也没有再工作
我呆在那里，看着他化掉的身体
从炼钢的岩浆里喷出来
然后我就走了
[ 喘气声 ]
我一定要发现到底这玩意从哪里来的
我想要了解文化背景
是什么可以激发我老爸
这么多的仇恨
我必须回到原点
你知道我找到了什么？
嗯？
我只是跟他们一样
或者这个钟
是我第一个战利品
我现在就要给你设一个
如果你不吐出那些钻石的话
[ 滴答声 ]
[ 叮 ]
你现在还有三分钟
[ 滴答声 ]
好吧
谁先来？
我来
不行
我先来
我先说得
你说了吗？
我去
我才不怕你呢
还没到时候
混蛋
麦克斯，你的肌肉是很牛逼
但是对找回我们的钱没有用
- 真的有必要这样吗？  - 你还要不要你那一份？
是，但是拜托，他是自己人。
“自己人”？
你真的跟他很熟嘛？
但是如果他真的什么都不知道呢?
-你在说什么呢？  - [ 嘲笑声 ]
如果那个位子上的人换做是你，会怎么样？
[ 笑声 ] 嘿，如果是我，我可不会在这里
[ 拍案而起 ]
哦，好吧，随便吧。
算你的了，大块头！
你这样拿不到钱的
不行吗？
不可能的
[ 笑声 ]
继续说。
不不不，我们不要太性急了
给他一点时间吧
遵守规则
你可是拷问过那批警察的
他们怎么说的？
好吧，他们怎么说得不重要
那些肮脏的警察太不可信了，你可信吗？
[ 笑声 ]
而且，如果他们真的有那家伙，我早就接管了
随你怎么折磨我，但是对你得到你那份没有任何帮助
[ 叹息声 ] 也许吧
[ 痛苦声 ]
但是我起码有点乐子了 [ 笑声 ]
[ 呻吟声 ]
[ 叮 ]
这种感觉真爽
[ 嘲笑声 ]
[ 呻吟声 ]
[ 惨叫，呜咽声 ]
数到三我停下来
[ 喘气，呻吟声 ]  一
二
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]  好吧
[ 惨叫声 ]
时间到！
[ 呻吟，喘气声 ]
- [ 惨叫声 ]  - 够了
上帝啊
[ 费什呻吟，喘气声 ]
[ 滴答声 ]
麦克斯，干得好!
你真的把你的手拿出来了吗？
- 看起来你好像能干的更漂亮  - 哦
这算下战书嘛？
很明显就是
好吧，你想放些钱来赌一把吗？
你们真的要赌这个吗？
这可是酷刑啊
不，不，这不算
还没到那一步呢
[ 笑声 ][ chuckling ]
你不会拖我们后腿吧，弗朗西斯？
[ 冷笑 ]
那么，这样如何？看我们哪一个先让他吐真言？
多少钱？
一千块？
鄙视你
好吧，五千
好吧，废柴，算你一个了
哦，兄弟，你上了贼船了
哦，杜克
你怎么不告诉我
这里已经有了这么多好玩的东东了
[ 笑声 ]
哦
你这个怀旧的家伙
你居然保存了我以前的工作鞋
[ 叹气 ] 好吧 ...
这个我一定好好保存
麦克斯，给你上一堂如何筷子使用课怎么样？
混蛋
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]
[ 笑声 ]
所以，你觉得呢，费什老弟？
你要说什么吗？
不是对你说的
太遗憾了
你要拿筷子干什么啊？
针灸
你觉得怎么样，伙计？
你想不想重新翻开你的记忆画卷吗？
[ 吐痰 ]
去死吧
看，这个态度可不太好
[ 叮 ] [ 嘶叫声 ]
[ 嘶叫声 ]
拜托，跟我说句话
有什么东西要吐槽嘛？
[ 嘶叫声 ]
现在呢？
没有嘛？
好吧
[ 嘶叫声 ]
现在，听我说
你一开口，我就拿开榔头，怎么样？
好
快点
好吧，我可算是警告过你的了
等等！
我记得了。
[ 克洛 ] 真的嘛？
真的嘛？
[ 克洛 ] 你想起什么了？
我想起来 --
[ 笑声 ] 我干过你的老妈
[ 笑声 ] [ laughing ]
跟我老妈？
跟我老妈
我会给你看什么叫“干我妈”。
- [ 杜克 ] 时间到  - [ 麦克斯偷笑 ]
我说了，时间到了！
哦！[ 笑声 ]
[ 笑声 ]
[ 笑声 ]  麦克斯是对的。
克洛
你就是个废柴.
[ 杜克 ] 克洛
克洛
[ 嘶叫声 ]
[ 车门打开 ]
[ 车子声 ]
我们出发了
♪ 摇滚音乐开始
啊
哦
哦，太完美了
太漂亮了
看着我
♪ 摇滚音乐
莫瑞斯
宝贝，看看你。
这么漂亮
莫瑞斯
-莫瑞斯  -这么了
有客来访
你看我干吗，为什么不去叫上拉比罗霍
出去让他们滚
[ 叹气 ]
夏尔莫
什么事
管道工？
谁叫的管道工？
你不会是把厕所又堵了吧?
那群家伙绝对有问题
嘿！你们不能停这里
嘿！混球！你们不能停这里
什么东东？
[ 惨叫声 ]
[ 喘气声 ]
举起手来！举起手来！
我说了他妈的举起手来！
我已经报警了，警察马上就到！
你们最好马上逃走！
是啊，好吧，趴下！
趴下！
别给我乱动！
你有什么更好的办法吗？
你休想得到这些钻石
我不是问你要！我只是说要拿走！
你们不知道这是谁的钻石！
很显然，不是偷你的
你看见这个没有？
这是一个纪念品
我每杀一个人就从他身上收集一个
你也想让我从你身上拿一个吗？
你不知道他们会怎么对我！
我更担心我们怎么对你，伙计！
[ 男声 ] 上帝啊，莫瑞斯
给他们想要的东西
闭嘴
是啊！闭嘴
[ 笑声 ]
我没有钥匙啊
[ 叹息 ]
没有关系
我有
不要啊
[ 喊叫声 ]
不要
别这样
[ 惨叫声 ]
我送给你一只手
哦，去死吧！
起来吧
哦上帝啊！
费什，快点！费什！
- 费什  - 费什，你搞什么
- 费什  - 费什
我靠
醒醒，兄弟，拜托！
快点！
勇敢一点，醒醒吧，快点
[ 呻吟声 ]
好吧
[ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
你醒了  [ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
[ 叫声 ][ grunting ]
干得不错，你确定他需要人工呼吸嘛？
[ 笑声 ][ chuckling ]  嗯，咬我了
[ 费什叹息 ]
[ 时钟开始 ]
你也在同一条船上
你怎么不去试试?
我在吃呢
你不想弄脏你的手吗？
你在这里做什么，弗朗西斯?
我说，如果你不想参与
也许你不想要你那一份了
你到底是我们一员，还是不算?
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]  哦，我当然是
但是我还想再坐等一会
我也在吃呢
你打算怎么样，用你臭脚熏死他吗？
[ 玻璃碾碎声 ]
[ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
我受不了那些娘们的玩意了
[ 笑声 ][ chuckling ]
[ 呻吟声 ]
去死吧
[ 叮 ]
你说什么
我听不见
[ 费什呻吟 ]
[ 呻吟 ]
好吧，大声点
说点什么吧，兄弟！
[ 呻吟 ]
[ 杜克 ] 时间到了！
麦克斯！我说时间到了！
靠！
我受不了这个游戏！
[ 喘气声 ][ panting ]
哦，你的袜子都湿了吧
小子
好吧，别生气
我的天
有本事坐我拳头上
[ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]  你想得美
[ 喘气 ]
你知道吗？
我想...
是时候了
[ 杜克 ] 啊啊啊，克洛
别忘记我们的耐心？
钟要被重新设置
[ 滴答声 ][ ticking ]
麦克斯，准备收钱了
[ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
[ 叹息 ]
嘿
[ 笑声 ][ chuckling ]
上帝啊
他下手还真得不轻啊。
好吧，我恐怕...
我非得靠近点来检查下
怎么了，弗朗西斯?
你吃不下了吗？
我有吗？
六年前你可不是这个样子的。
老大，今时不同往日阿
我现在可是有孩子的人了
[ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
现在，张开你的嘴，说“啊”
哦，拜托啊
嘿
搞定以后我会奖赏你一颗棒棒糖，好吗？
好，你听着
你可以选择舒服的方式，也可以选择难受点的方式
你今晚为什么要我们来？
我没有强迫你们做任何事情
为什么？
好吧  [ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
[ 惨叫声 ]
我以为你也许想要你那一份
你不是太他妈需要钱了吗？
你居然会大发善心了?
这不是发善心
[ 惨叫声 ]
就是这样
好样的
我知道你的目的
是吗？
你也这样告诉你门外守着的朋友嘛？
[ 滴答声继续 ]
- [ 哭声 ]  - 现在...
你该说了，或者你永远不要说了
[ 哭声 ] [ groaning ]  [ 笑声 ] [ laughing ]
你说什么？
你懂的。
- [ 铃声响起 ]  - [ 惨叫声 ]
是的
我恐怕
你的蛀牙的确很多
我们还要拔掉一些
你去哪里？
该死的洗手间
现在的小孩子真不懂礼貌
[ 擤鼻涕 ]
[ 吐痰 ]
[ 打碎 ]
[ 深呼吸 ]
老爸弱爆了
[ 吸气 ]
[ 心跳声 ]
[ 嘶叫声 ]
哦
你懂得，在州立监狱里
牙科保健真是严重缺乏  [ 笑声 ][ chuckles ]
我觉得我发现更多蛀虫的孔
好吧好吧好吧
怎么了？
我说
- 我会说出来  - 你会？
好的，你知道我们已经玩过这个游戏了，费什
你知道你再说谎会怎么样?
好，说吧
你- 你是对的
我吗？
好吧，太奇妙了
关于什么呢？
钻石
你没说过
我- 警察在追我
[ 嘎嘎声 ]
蛇的眼睛
他们越来越接近
快点
那怎么样？
[ 喘气 ]
我没有任何办法
那钻石现在在哪里？
你放在哪里了？
我没有办法
费什，钻石到底在哪里？
麦克斯！你想干嘛？
告诉我们在哪里？
我的钱啊！
我的钱呢？
费什
拜托，费什
拜托，说句话
啊，上帝啊
嘿，嘿，别，别动，别乱动
我去叫救护车
不要不要
[ 呻吟声 ]
尼尔森，你个混蛋！
我们在哪里？
戴上你们的面具
[ 克洛 ] 怎么回事啊？
狗屎！
[ 痛苦声 ] 啊，我看车子不能用了
- [ 远处警笛在响 ]  - 我勒个去，他们这么追来了
在北面
我们得离开这里
内尔森
内尔森！
- [ 警笛声 ]  - 哦，完蛋
- 快点，我们走  - 我们赶紧得离开这里
啊，去死吧！
你这个混蛋，这是我受伤的手
- 啊，完蛋，他们又接近了  - 走啊，走啊！
嘿，菜鸟！别忘了包！
[ 叫声 ][ grunting ]
嘿，兄弟！
[ 警笛声接近 ]  [ 弗朗西斯 ] 分散！分散！
他死了！
你这个脑残！他死了！
什么？
- 他死了！  - 你确定?
我不是医生，但是我很肯定，他死了！
我们要他留他活口，麦克斯！哦，我知道了，我知道了！
你搞砸这个事，就跟你搞砸警察那边的事一个样
我没做错任何事，一派胡言
胡扯！你真是彻头彻尾的失败！
跟你那个老爸一模一样
- 你  - 哦，哦，哦，来啊
哦哦！给我个不杀你的理由
哦，你这个混蛋
你还不懂吗，这个白痴？
我们再也得不到任何消息了
游戏结束了！
把你的枪拿开
就是因为你，我们现在什么都得不到了
我们本来就得不到
你这是什么意思？
整个晚上就是一场闹剧
我不干了，杜克
你没得选
我走了
- 还没完呢，弗朗西斯  - 够了
哦，我想跟我对着干嘛？
你难道觉得我会让你从这里走出去吗？
怎么回事？
告诉他们你的真实目的，杜克
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]
他们知道的
他们知道？未了之事？
天杀的钻石
你们什么时候能醒醒啊？
唯一的未了之事就是我们
你说什么呢？我们中计了吗？
他让我们了结了费什
然后就是我们
这个想法有点难以理解
[ 弗朗西斯 ] 不是吗？
你很聪明，克洛，好好想想
他买通了警察，搞定了钻石，嫁祸给费什
就是被麦克斯杀掉的那批警察
六年以后，费什出来了，我们都要死
他拿走我们的钱，毫无疑问
没有未了的事
干得太漂亮了，不是吗？
嗯，我猜这就是为什么警察就在外面暴雨中守着，不是吗？
什么？还有警察？
是啊，事实就是
他们正在窃听我们这里所有的对话
好吧，弗朗西斯，他们在哪里？
你装了窃听器吧？
[ 弗朗西斯冷笑 ]
是啊
我是装了窃听器
那你脱下衬衣让我们看看
库鲁，什么时候能睁开眼睛看清楚？你是个傀儡啊
解开你的衬衣
你知道你被他操纵了多久了啊？
弗朗西斯，解开你的衬衣！
或者呢？
你想开枪吗？
如果你想开枪，你就开吧！
[ 麦克斯 ] 快证明给他们你没有窃听器，兄弟
也许我们就能相信你的鬼话了
是啊，怎么样，弗朗西斯？
[ 冷笑 ] 证明给你看？
为什么，麦克斯？
你甚至还不如克洛
至少杜克还把他当个人来看
我是你的话，可不会这么说
你？
你只是一条狗
杜克只是轻轻打个响指，你就帮他扑出去咬人
你就是他的婊子
狗项圈的感觉怎么样？
[ 枪声 ]
我们只是他的筹码
还有一些跟他一路的警察要拿我们的钱呢
麦克斯，你在干什么呢？
我已经受不了这个猫捉老鼠的游戏了
我只要我那一份
你不会这么做的
我不是你的狗
放下枪
这个混蛋已经算计了我们六年了
[ 笑声 ] 原来你相信了躺在地上那摊屎说的话
我不相信你们任何人
麦克斯，
如果我要杀你
你早就死了
[ 麦克斯 ] 也许吧
也许相反
麦克斯，放下你的枪
除非我拿到我的钱
听着，你太傻了，弗朗西斯一派胡言
他一直谎话连篇
如果他骗我们，那窃听器在哪里
在洗手间啊，傻瓜，他去过洗手间
- 你就这么确定吗？  - 是啊
嘿。杜克什么时候坑过我们了？
没关系，我们又不是什么“三个好朋友”
”一荣俱荣，一损俱损“，兄弟
那是”三个火枪手“，你这个文盲
你自认很聪明
觉得你聪明到可以躲过一颗子弹？
[ 杜克 ] 好吧，孩子们
让我们一起冷静一下
这个怎么样，废柴？
你有多聪明？
好吧，我是废柴，我来证明给你看我有多聪明
聪明到知道你爸在你家卧室里都做过些什么事情
干你！
不，干你老爸
跟你一样
[ 枪声 ]
[ 叫声 ][ grunting ]
- [ 呻吟声 ]  - [ 扳机 ]
[ 呻吟声 ]
我还站着呢
衰人
[ 喘息,笑 ]
嘿
[ 呻吟声 ]
哦，不
我要去医院
杜克
你在干什么啊
我要去医院
[ 哭声 ]
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]
哦，别这样，杜克
在我们这么多年出生入死后？
让你死在自己
杀戮的战场吧
混蛋，我可是站在你那一边的啊
我这么爱你，你这个狗娘养的--
[ 倒地声 ]
再见.
[ 轻轻地哭声 ]
嗯
[ 喘气声 ][ exhales ]
[ 哼声 ]
好吧，
事情很顺利
只剩下我们两个了
[ 筷子声 ]
我运气不好，还是没找到我的钻石
所以，你不得不成为我的安慰奖了
但是我们不要猴急
一个智者曾经这么写道，
如果我今晚不能看见她，
那我只得放弃她
所以，我要吃
河豚肉“
[ 打响指 ] 哦！
最直接的快感
哦
更有感觉了
[ 雷声 ]
[ 呼吸声很重 ]
河豚肉用正确的方式切得的，
可以是很美味  真是一部惊悚片
但是我没想到
那个毒素渗透到你身体这么快
- [ 呼吸急促 ]  - 所以
我们要抓紧时间了
哦
哦，我敢打赌
如果你现在能说话
你会问我
为什么？
好吧
长话短说，你拿走了
我的东西
[ 细语 ] 现在我想要回来
[ 雪茄扣的声音 ]
也许这个可以让你想起点什么
[ 男人喘气声 ] [ 女人哭声 ]
好的
[ 哭声 ]
好，嘿，你怎么样？
你没事吧？还好吗？
没事
是啊，我没事
好的。我们没事了
好的，那我现在去看看他们吧。
-好吗？  -好的
你没事了
呆在这里，我马上回来
[ 喘息声 ]
[ 哭声 ]
[ 深呼吸 ]
[ 克洛叫喊 ]尼尔森，你这个混蛋！
[ 弗朗西斯 ] 我们在哪里？
嘿，菜鸟！别忘了包！
[ 弗朗西斯 ] 完了！完了！  [ 警笛靠近声 ]
[ 警笛靠近声 ]  [ 弗朗西斯 ] 狗屎！
分开走！
你知道，
我不太懂黑社会的那一套
但是--
你似乎属于那种很会唬人的那类
也许你要换个新的游戏了
机会--
[ 子弹取下 ] 真的不是好东西
一个这么小小的东西
可以毁灭一切
[ 枪扳上扳机 ]
六年前
我从未想过有一天我会站在这里
我真要感谢你改变了我的生活
[ 按下扳机 ]
一开始我是这么想的
好吧，也许
快乐是可以用钱买的
但是，有些东西，你就是买不到
[ 按下扳机 ]
钱买不回我的美好生活
而且钱
钱没法带回给我，我的爱
[ 按下扳机 ]
但是这个--
这个感觉
真是太好了
别
♪ [ 布鲁士音乐 ]
[ 汽车引擎声 ]
现在去哪里？
我只想回家
♪ [ 音乐继续 ]
♪ [ 男颤音 ]
♪ 我只是无法忍受失去你
♪ 所以我看见
我们分手了
♪ 继续走
♪ 我留下的，只有我
♪无谓的傲慢
[ 女伴唱 ] 让我躲藏，让我掩盖
♪我的眼泪和悲伤
♪你给我
♪你伤害了我
♪ 当你说再见
♪ 那就请你走吧
♪ 哦妈妈
♪ 让你永远看不见我的泪水
走吧♪ walk
♪ 我祈求你
♪ 走吧，走吧
♪ 哦  走♪ walk
♪ 永远不让你看见我的眼泪
♪ 走吧
♪ 我祈求你，我祈求你  走♪ walk
♪ 走吧，走吧
♪ 走吧  ♪ 永远不让你看见我的眼泪
♪ 走吧
走♪ walk
♪ 我的眼睛里没有灰尘  ♪ 走吧
走吧♪ walk
♪ 我的眼泪不是因为那些浓烟
是因为你伤害了我
♪ 我不想让你看见这个男人的眼泪  走♪ walk
♪ 所以，请你走
♪ 走吧
♪ 哦，亲爱的，不
走♪ walk
♪ 走吧